Hello Hello Friends Welcome Back Today
in this video we are going to show
how insurance of a private vehicle is deducted
from the CSC portal, bike, Kia, whichever company's
vehicle you have, you
can deduct insurance from the CSC portal and sell it to the customer,
you will also earn a good income,
so let's start,
log in to the CSC portal,
click on insurance, scroll down here, click on
motor third party,
click on it, whichever
company's service is active in the CSC portal, you
can take a policy from that service, right now I am going to
take a policy from ICICI company, this is showing
such a company that Yuva Sangh will do
insurance policy in two ways, ghee, Abhitak Pati Cars are going to do,
click on Kartik,
click on Geet, registration details,
enter the registration number of the vehicle,
click on Get Started Details,
you have to take the RC book from the customer and
look at it, type the registration number,
registration number is given so that you can
fill in the complete details of Yuva Vahini, you have
filled in all these details, registration
state, state manufacturer, which
company's model, how will the policy be
started, details  Engine number, chassis number,
type, manufacturer, you have to match it after seeing the details,
you can leave the description
here, it is telling individual here, personal
accident cover is telling here, if you have already
taken a policy, then let it be the only one, if you do
not have a policy for it now, then
remove it, from here it is
telling no here, so
if you keep this for 6000 during this period, then if the third party
damage is more than 6000, then the
company will not pay, if you note it, then the
company will pay whatever the third party damage is, keep in mind that there is no here,
if you click yes, then it is telling here
insurance policy details are available, if
you already have a policy, then if you say yes,
you will get an option to enter the insurance policy
number, so keep it no,
click on get, it will show how much the policy is going to
cost, the rate of the policy has been
shown, Rs 2828 total
premium will have to be paid, the details of this will be entered by making the
payment to the video eyes or insurance,
they have to enter the nominee
name, nominee relative  For Nach Nominated,
customer details have to be entered. Vehicle owner name has to be
entered. To enter that egg,
click on Create New Customer.
Title has to be selected. Whether it is Mr., Mrs. or Ms.
or Mister, select it.
Complete details of the end have to be entered. Name has to be
entered. Birthday has to be entered. Address has to be entered.
Length mark can be left. Pin code has to be
entered. City has to be entered. This is tempered glass.
Email ID has to be entered. Mobile number has to be entered.
PAN number can be left. After
filling the complete details there, click on the portal at the gate. You will get the
payment option. You will make the payment from there. You have to take the
Aadhar document of the vehicle and enter it after
seeing it. Details of the mantra have to be entered.
From here you have to select it.
Pin code has to be entered. Select here to
automatically select the district.
Enter the email ID. Enter the email ID.
Enter the mobile number.
Match the details of the vehicle and also
match the details of the bank. Check it once.
Click on Poshan at the gate. Repayment has to be made.
Click on Bike Policy.
Amount 2828 is showing. Violet Amount  I am going to
subscribe for Rs 2732. I have to
enter the SSC password and click on Brigade. I have to
enter the CSC VLE PIN. I have to click on
subscribe details. I have to
click on UP. I can print it
out and see it for the customer. I have
come to the CBSE portal. See
how much commission it takes. In third party
insurance, the school has to be opened below. It is
showing here CSC refer number 57.
Buy more. I had told the customer
Rs 2828, so here you have got Rs 2732, you have made a profit of about Rs 960
and I have to subscribe to the insurance.
Thanks for watching. If you liked the video, then
like and subscribe to the channel. See you
in the next video.